Show More
Show More Do it do it
[Music]
Show More
Do it
what a dull life it is friend You will wake up in the morning and work Come and sleep at
night Then wake up in the morning and work Go and sleep at
night Then wake up in the morning and
work Go and sleep at night Then wake up in the morning and work Go and sleep at
night Then wake up in the
morning and work Go and sleep at night Then wake up in the morning and work Go and sleep at night Then
what a day it was
friend When we were kids we used to have so much fun
friend [
Music]
[Music]
190 The bastard will copy me Where are you
Do it it has been
confirmed It was known that on the issue of
[Music] on
Wednesday
[Music] you had
help So looted you had
President of India DR [
Music] There is
bhindi bhindi Do it
hey firecracker Rohit Sharma Its exactly this question
SP has a lot more to do it
we will play gilli danda The four worlds can go to
hell The tag will leave Delhi and hit you straight
in the ass Loot
this issue Turn it on
You are angry with me
Today on the date what
juice will you apply You send it, it is not in my control You have
sent it, let's do it  So do it
soon, do it
sister, do it, do it, the
movie
alarm clock is off, robbers are looting, hey, the
guard is not full, it is torn, see, it is torn, my
ass is torn, that
they are
hands-free, then only the words are left
[Music] do it
and tell me we have been
looted [
Music] it happened, take up the
issue of do it, birthday 500 rupees valley, torn apart,
lovers sitting, sitting, sitting,
sitting, in the mind, la la la la la
[Music]
do it,
plain mode, kabaddi, chicken bone ₹100 per
kg, trees and plants, loafer, shoes, take the money
[Music]
that against Chautala, then tell me guys, then that is
our childhood draw and guide, hmm, any one is
good, do like the video
and tell me in the comments, how did you like it,
we used to stand every day, which you found
very cool and you will get it here and if
you like the 501 with a help, then you
bastard, please do tell me and thank you,
this is enough and we will meet in the next video, till then
bye-bye